temcam.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy of Temcam - Temcam

Thanks for stopping by here, if you think that you need more information or if you have doubts/questions/feedback/corrections about our legal privacy policy page then please don’t hesitate to contact us on our official email address.

At temcam.com, the privacy of our visitors/readers/users is of high importance. This legal privacy policy document describes the data which we receive in various form on temcam.com and how its used and collected by our servers.

##  Log Files 

Like so many other Web Sites over Internet, temcam.com does use log files and makes legal use of it. The type of information inside our log files includes various required information like internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser along with its version, Internet Service Provider (ISP), exact date as well as time, referring website and exit pages, amount of clicks to analyze the behavior, track visitor’s movement inside the site, exact demographic information, etc.

We do accept and promise that we will never fetch information regarding our visitors personal identification. And the information which we log (as mentioned above) don’t link to any of the thing which can give us information regarding the personal data of users.

##  Cookies And Web Beacons 

As stated above also, temcam.com does use cookies as well as web beacons so that it can store information about visitors as well as users this helps us to record user-specific information and details so that users can access the website.

**DoubleClick Dart Cookie  **

  1. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies as we are part of publisher in Google Adsense program to serve ads on this site
  2. The above mentioned, DART cookie helps to serve user and location based ads on temcam.com as well as other sites available on Internet
  3. If opt out of this, please visit this URL : <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

As stated above only some of our advertising partners may use cookies, it includes Google Adsense, Yahoo Media Ads, Bing, Chitika, etc

All these third-party ad servers or advertising companies use special kind of technology to advertisement, and the ads that are shown on temcam.com have nothing to do with us. These networks receive users’ IP address when they click on their advertisements (which may include banner/text/video/flash)

We hereby declare that temcam.com don’t have any access over these collected data (IP, demographics, etc) from our partnered advertisement networks.

If you think that you may require more details about the information collected by those networks then you are free to consult their privacy policy documents.

If you still wish to disable cookies then their are various options available in your respective web browsers you are free to do so.

If you have any doubt then feel free to contact us!
